yourvideofile.org 2019-04-26

# Privacy Policy & Terms Of Service..

**Terms of service:** Usage of this website and all provided products is subject to compliance of your country's legal permissions, if your local laws do not permit downloads and audio conversions of online videos you are not allowed to use this service. You are also not permitted to use this utility to infringe any sort of copyright by downloading multimedia content which you don't have rights to use or is not open-source. Also, this addon/service is not associated in anyway with Youtube - which is a trademark of Google.

**What do we use your information for?**

We respect our user's privacy and DO NOT COLLECT ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION, and only following STANDARD web-analytic information is ever recorded:

; Analytic to measure traffic and improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

; We use Google and other reputed (safe from malware and adware) ad-serving platforms from third party vendor to provide free services to non-pro users (And that also **ONLY** when visiting our websites), which utilizes cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [https://www.yourvideofile.org](https://www.yourvideofile.org/)

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 31 July 2016

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

https://www.yourvideofile.org  
contact@yourvideofile.org
